[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "50 years of marriage are known as this.", "correct_answer": "Gold anniversary", "incorrect_answers": ["Pearl anniversary", "Diamond anniversary", "Platinum anniversary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries has adopted the rose as its national flower?", "correct_answer": "England", "incorrect_answers": ["Turkey", "France", "Spain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country has the largest number of gum producers, with over 60 gum factories.", "correct_answer": "Turkey", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "USA", "Russia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many days are the crew members home from their latest trip, before they set out on their ill fated trip in The Perfect Storm?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "5", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the diet of all kangaroos consist of in general?", "correct_answer": "Plant matter", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Fungi", "Plant and animal matter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous supermodel was one of the coyotes in the 2000 comedy drama movie Coyote Ugly?", "correct_answer": "Tyra Banks", "incorrect_answers": ["Adriana Lima", "Gisele Bundchen", "Alek Wek"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This London style porter has the flavor of chocolate and coffee incorporated into the brewing process for a unique tasting adventure.", "correct_answer": "Blackhook", "incorrect_answers": ["Bud", "Winterhook", "Copperhook"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first mate of PT-73, that was commanded by Lieutenant Commander Quinton McHale?", "correct_answer": "Ensign Charles Parker", "incorrect_answers": ["Fuji Kobiaji", "Lt. Elroy Carpenter", "Captain Wallace B. Binghamton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is the yogurt Zabady produced?", "correct_answer": "Egypt", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "South Africa", "Ghana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of the four nucleotides that make up Deoxyribo-Nucleic Acid (DNA), which of the following is a purine?", "correct_answer": "Adenine", "incorrect_answers": ["Cytosine", "Proline", "Thymine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This pop singer, songwriter and pianist, who attended the highly regarded Julliard School of Music, recorded two different versions of the song Breaking Up Is Hard to Do.", "correct_answer": "Neil Sedaka", "incorrect_answers": ["Steven Tyler", "Neil Diamond", "Andy Williams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the city of Eilat founded?", "correct_answer": "1951", "incorrect_answers": ["1939", "1941", "1929"]}]